Contact

21997261187 (Mobile) contato@gabrielvalle.com.br

www.linkedin.com/in/bielvalle (LinkedIn) www.gabrielvalle.com.br (Personal)

Top Skills

Web Design
Graphic Design
User Interface Design

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) Inglês (Professional Working)

Certifications

Javascript

Gabriel Valle

Interface Designer & Developer

Rio de Janeiro, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

Summary

English:

Designer and Developer. Degree in industrial design. Professional experienced of over ten years with graphic design and web design. Differentials in interface design and front-end developer. Photoshop, Html, Css and JavaScript Specialist. Facility for teamwork and project leadership.

Português:

Designer e Developer. Graduação em desenho industrial. Experiência profissional de mais dez anos com design gráfico e web design. Diferenciais em design de interface e programação frontend. Especialista em Photoshop, Html, Css e Javascript. Facilidade com trabalho em equipe e liderança de projetos.

Experience

Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Rio de Janeiro Senior Frontend Developer September 2018 - Present Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Html, Sass, Javascript & Angular.

MJV Technology & Innovation Technology Consultant January 2018 - August 2018 (8 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Html, Sass, Javascript, Angular.

Bradesco Seguros UI Designer January 2018 - August 2018 (8 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

UI Designer Specialist

Repense Comunicação Frontend Developer June 2017 - November 2017 (6 months)

Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Angular.

Estrellar Design & Programação Frontend Developer November 2015 - May 2017 (1 year 7 months)

Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Html, Css, Javascript, Node, Express, Angular, React, Vue, Mongo, Ionic.

Ycloud Inc.

Frontend Developer January 2015 - October 2015 (10 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Html, Css, Javascript, Angular.

CasaDigital.com
Frontend Developer
June 2014 - December 2014 (7 months)
Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Html, Css, Javascript, Angular, Phonegap.

LegoBranding.com.br
UI Designer
July 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 6 months)
Rio de Janeiro, Recreio dos Bandeirantes, Brasil

UI/UX Design. Sketches, Wireframes, Interfaces, Responsive, Sitemaps, Personas, Card Sorting, Eye Tracking.

Webmotors
UI Designer
February 2012 - June 2012 (5 months)
Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

UI/UX Design. Sketches, Wireframes, Interfaces, Responsive, Sitemaps, Personas, Card Sorting, Eye Tracking.

AgenciaLego.com.br Web Designer June 2010 - January 2012 (1 year 8 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Criação de layouts, wireframes, interfaces, banners e newsletters; Desenvolvimento de sites em HTML, CSS, JS. Padrões W3C.

Ad5 advertising
Web Designer
January 2010 - May 2010 (5 months)
Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Criação de layouts, wireframes, interfaces, banners e newsletters;

Desenvolvimento de sites em HTML, CSS, JS. Padrões W3C.

Grupo Blend Comunicação Web Designer November 2008 - November 2009 (1 year 1 month) Rio de Janeiro e Barra da Tijuca, Brasil

Criação de layouts, wireframes, interfaces, banners e newsletters; Desenvolvimento de sites em HTML, CSS, JS. Padrões W3C.

Birô Serviços & Comércio Graphic Designer September 2007 - October 2008 (1 year 2 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Criação de identidade visual, logotipos, impressos e diagramação de revistas; Tratamento das imagens; Photoshop, Indesign e Illustrator. Diagramação de Guias, Livros e Revistas.

Infoartes Soluções Gráficas Graphic Designer January 2006 - June 2007 (1 year 6 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Criação de identidade visual, logotipos, impressos e diagramação de revistas; Tratamento das imagens; Photoshop, Indesign e Illustrator. Diagramação de Guias, Livros e Revistas.

Guia do Comércio Jornais & Revistas Graphic Designer December 2004 - October 2005 (11 months) Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Criação de identidade visual, logotipos, impressos e diagramação de revistas; Tratamento das imagens; Photoshop, Indesign e Illustrator. Diagramação de Guias, Livros e Revistas.

INSS

Internship

February 2004 - November 2004 (10 months)

Rio de Janeiro Area, Brazil

Estagiário com funções voltadas para o atendimento interno com consultas em sistemas de intranet além de manutenção e controle do protocolo processual da agência.

Education

Instituto Infnet

Bachelor's degree, Desenho Industrial · (2010 - 2015)

Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Rio de Janeiro

Design - Mídia Digital, Industrial and Product Design · (2019 - 2022)

Universidade Estácio de Sá

Bachelor of Laws, Direito · (2006 - 2010)

Udacity Brasil

Engineer's degree, Information Technology · (2018 - 2018)

Udemy Academy

Course Programming front-end JavaScript and jQuery, Webmaster, Developer, Programmer, Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2016 - 2017)